Guide to the Communications Workers of America Records Addendum WAG.124.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Communications Workers of America Records Addendum
1939-1998, (Bulk 1970-1995)
1970-1995
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Communications Workers of America
WAG.124.001
199 Linear Feet in 199 boxes
The Communications Workers of America (CWA), founded in 1947 as an industrial union of telephone industry workers, is now one of the largest unions in the United States with a diverse membership, including an active public employees division. For the most part, this Addendum to the Archive's CWA collection (Wagner #124) documents the activities of the CWA from the 1970s to the mid-1990s. It includes records of organizing, bargaining, and technological advances in the telecom industry. It consists largely of President's Office records from the administration of Morton Bahr, as well as Secretary-Treasurer's Office records, Vice-President's Office records (John C. Carroll), files of presidential assistants (Lou Gerber and John Morgan), and records from the Contract Compliance, Printing, Publishing and Media Workers, Public Affairs, Public and Health Care Workers and Research sectors or departments. The records document all aspects of union operations: organizing, collective bargaining, contract administration, strikes, grievances, arbitrations, political action and relations with the AFL-CIO and with other unions. NOTE: This collection is housed offsite and advance notice is required for use.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by the Communications Workers of America, 2002. The accession number associated with this gift is 2001.174.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
The organization of the Communications Workers of America (CWA) in 1947 was the culmination of nearly a half-century of struggle for telephone unionism. Until the middle 1890s there was very little union activity among telephone workers. In 1898 the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) began to try to organize some of the telephone linemen and cable splicers. Numerous strikes by the IBEW in the 1910s were unsuccessful as the Bell Telephone Company used its monopolistic control over the industry to defeat telephone unionism. However, during these years there was an upsurge of union membership among telephone operators mostly centered in Boston. A joint organizing campaign by the IBEW and Women's Trade Union League was very successful and won major concessions in 1914-1915. However, after a failed strike in 1919, the Bell Company began to aggressively promote company unions and aggressively fought all organizing drives.
Telephone unions found that it was very difficult to organize an industry in which the Bell Company had monopolistic control and almost unlimited resources. The company took advantage of the fact that telephone workers were geographically dispersed and the conversion to dial telephones made the system less vulnerable to labor slowdowns. Bell's hiring practices assured that the vast majority of telephone workers were relatively highly educated, native-born Caucasians who were well spoken in English. Telephone operators were predominately young women who tended to work for only a few years before marrying and having families. These workforce demographics made union organizing difficult.
The passage of the Wagner Act in 1936, which removed all the legal barriers to industrial union organization, reinvigorated the campaign for telephone unionism. However, progress was slow as telephone workers were for the most part insulated from the worst effects of the Great Depression. The Bell Company's response to the Wagner Act that outlawed company unions was to transform them into so-called independent labor organizations (non AFL or CIO) that could claim to be in compliance with national labor laws. During the early CIO years from 1937 through 1942 union organizing proceeded slowly in the telephone industry. The focus was on amalgamating the various local unions that were plant, craft, or district based into a national federation.
In 1939 the National Federation of Telephone Workers (NFTW) was formed but this organization was weak and decentralized. Stagnant wages and deteriorating working conditions during World War II stimulated telephone worker solidarity and union amalgamation. When Joseph A. Beirne was elected President of NFTW in 1943 the union began a full-scale organizing campaign. In 1946 there was a nation wide strike that led to the first national agreement with the American Telephone and Telegraph Company (AT & T). However, recognizing the weakness of the NFTW structure AT & T forced another strike in 1947. When this strike collapsed the NFTW structure fell apart and the CWA was born.
During the next twenty-five years the CWA under the leadership of Joseph A. Beirne moved aggressively to organize telephone workers across the United States. AT & T, with its monopolistic control of long-distance ("long lines") service, resisted. Not until 1974, after years of labor-management unrest and a series of strikes, did AT&T agree to system-wide collective bargaining. Shortly after the national contract was signed Joseph A. Beirne died. He was succeeded as President by CWA Secretary-Treasurer Glenn E. Watts.
In the 1980s the CWA began to expand beyond telecommunications creating a Public Employees Department that successfully organized 34,000 New Jersey state workers in 1981. In 1985 Morton Bahr became the CWA President. In 1987 the CWA merged with the International Typographical Workers Union. In 1992 both the National Association of Broadcast Employees and the Newspaper Guild became part of the CWA's Printing, Publishing and Media Workers division. As of this writing the CWA is one of the United States' strongest unions with more than 600,000 members.
Scope and Content Note
The CWA Records, Addendum is arranged in 11 series, described below:
Series I: Files of the President's Office, 1970-1997:
Sub-series I:A: Correspondence, 1985-1997 includes incoming and outgoing correspondence between CWA national headquarters and districts, local officers, members, and other individuals and organizations.
Sub-series I:B: Bargaining Files, 1982-1997, includes notes on meetings and correspondence with management, contracts, negotiations materials, and data relating to other labor organizations.
Sub-series I:C: General Files, 1970-1996, includes files on the AFL-CIO, CWA committees, conferences, financial contributions, conventions, CWA departments and divisions, Executive Board minutes, U.S. government departments, legislation, political action, organizing, and public relations.
Sub-series I:D: consists of records relating to the J.A. Beirne Foundation and the Joseph A. Bierne and Ray Hackney Scholarship Funds, 1977-1998, including files on grants, scholarships awarded, and student correspondence.
Sub-series I:E: Membership Files and Staff Activity Reports,1980-1988, includes files on dues-related matters, and district and national staff Activity Reports.
Series II: Files of the Secretary-Treasurer's Office, 1939-1993, includes material on relations with the AFL-CIO, the Democratic National Committee, and CWA Districts, as well as financial statements, pension files, strategic planning files and records of the Budget Review Committee and Ways and Means Committee.
Series III: Files of Vice-President John C. Carroll, 1958-1992, includes material on the AFL-CIO, AT&T, arbitrations, bargaining, the Bell System, divestiture, grievances, health care, "Jobs with Justice," the CWA Legal Department, and memoranda of agreement, as well as general correspondence.
Series IV: Correspondence of Lou Gerber, Legislative Staff, 1973-1982. Chronological file of legislative correspondence.
Series V: Files of John Morgan, Legislative Assistant to the President, 1966-1996, includes correspondence, files on Federal Communications Commission Hearings, legislative material and files relating to foreign trade issues.
Sub-series V:A: Correspondence, 1969-1994.
Sub-series V:B: FCC Hearings, Rulings and Court Cases, 1966-1995.
Sub-series V:C: General Files, 1973-1996.
Series VI: Files of the Contract Compliance Section, 1971-1995. Files relate to Alltel, AT&T, Bell System, Centel, Contel, GTE, NYNEX, United Telephone Company, US West, and Western Electric
Series VII: Files of the Internal Communications Section, 1986-1988. Includes files relating to Communications School, general correspondence, newsletters, and staff personal histories
Series VIII: Contract Correspondence of the Printing, Publishing and Media Workers Sector (PPMWS) Section, 1986.
Sub-series VIII:A: Mailers Unions, Local 3-Local 167.
Sub-series VIII:B: Typographical Unions, Local 1-Local 969.
Series IX: Files of the Public Affairs Section, 1983-1991, includes material relating to AT&T, bargaining, conventions, Northern Telecom, public relations, as well as clippings, press releases and news summaries.
Series X: Files of the Public and Health Care Workers Section, 1986-1995, includes material on the AFL-CIO, the A. Philip Randolph Institute, conventions, CWA district, Executive Board meetings, CWA locals, pay equity, public and health-care workers, and the Texas State Employees Union, as well as general correspondence.
Series XI: Files of the Research Department, 1947-1998. Primarily bargaining-related records.
Sub-series XI:A: AT&T, Ameritech, Bargaining, Bell System, Correspondence, Council on Wage and Price Stability, Employee/Salary Reports, MCI, National Information Infrastructure, NYNEX, Northern Telecom, Occupational Job Evaluation, Pacific Telecom, Quality of Work Life, Strike Press Coverage, Technology, Wage-Price Guidelines, Western Electric.
Sub-series XI:B: Arbitration Cases (Microfiche).
Arrangement
Series are arranged alphabetically by topic within each series, and chronologically within topics.
The files are grouped into 11 series:
Missing Title
I, Files of the President's Office (Morton Bahr)
II, Files of the Secretary-Treasurer's Office
III, Files of Vice-President John C. Carroll
IV, Correspondence of Lou Gerber, Legislative Staff
V, Files of John Morgan, Legislative Assistant to the President
VI, Files of the Contract Compliance Section
VII, Files of the Internal Communications Section
VIII, Contract Correspondence of the Printing, Publishing and Media Workers Sector (PPMWS) Section
IX, Files of the Public Affairs Section
X, Files of the Public and Health Care Workers Section
XI, Files of the Research Section
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Sub-series XI:B: Arbitration Cases contains microfiche
Labor unions -- Elections -- United States.; Labor unions -- Telecommunication -- United States.; American Telephone and Telegraph Company -- Employees.; Affirmative Action programs.; Clippings (information artifacts); Strikes and lockouts -- Telecommunication.; Telecommunication -- Employees -- United States.; Labor unions -- Organizing -- United States.; Legal documents.; Discrimination in employment.; Telecommunication -- United States -- History.; Reports.; Minutes (administrative records); Telecommunication -- Law and legislation -- United States.; Financial records; Labor unions -- Political activity -- United States.; Labor unions -- Contract administration.; Correspondence.; Arbitration, Industrial.; Collective labor agreements -- Telecommunication.; Fliers (printed matter); Corporate divestiture -- United States.; Labor unions -- Officials and employees.; American Telephone and Telegraph Company; Carroll, John C.; Bahr, Morton; Easterling, Barbara; Gerber, Lou.; Bell Telephone Company; Joseph A. Beirne Memorial Foundation; Mancino, Larry.; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers; Morgan, John T.; Southern Federation of Telephone Workers; United Telephone Employees; Watts, Glenn E.; Western Electric Company; McGovern, George S. (George Stanley), 1922-; International Confederation of Free Trade Unions; AFL-CIO; Beirne, Joseph A., 1911-; Postal, Telegraph and Telephone Workers' International; Communications Workers of America
- Series I: Files of the Presidents Office, 1970-1998.
  - Subseries I:A: Correspondence, 1985-1997.
    - Administration I, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Administration II, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - AT&T, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Arbitration, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Bargaining, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bargaining Units, Jan 1992-Jul 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bargaining Units: AT&T, Jan 1993-Aug 1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bargaining Units: AT&T, Sep 1993-Dec 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - CWA-City Council (various) Correspondence, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Companies, CWA Member Employers, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Contributions, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Contributions, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Defense/Strike Fund, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - District 1, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - District 1, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - District 1, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - District 1, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - District 2, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - District 3, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - District 4, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - District 6, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - District 7, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - District 7, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - District 7, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - District 8, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - District 9, 1986-1991 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - District 10, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - District 11, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - District 12, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - District 13, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Executive Board, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Executive Board, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Executive Vice-President, Oct 1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Executive Vice-President, Nov 1986-Dec 1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Federal Communications Commission, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - General, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Grievances, 1989-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Grievances, Jan 1996-Apr 1996 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Grievances, May 1996-Dec 1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - International, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - International, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - International, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - International, Jan 1994-Aug 1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - International, Sep 1994-Dec 1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - International, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - International, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Job References, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Job References, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Job References, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Local Officers, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Local Presidents, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Locals, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Mancino, Larry, Apr 1991-Jul 1991 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Mancino, Larry, Aug 1991-Sep 1991 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Mancino, Larry, Oct 1991-Dec 1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Mancino, Larry, Jan 1992 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Mancino, Larry, Feb 1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Mancino, Larry, Mar 1992 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Mancino, Larry, Apr 1992-Jun 1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Mancino, Larry, Jul 1992-Sep 1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Mancino, Larry, Oct 1992-Dec 1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Mancino, Larry, Jan 1993-Feb 1993 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Mancino, Larry, Mar 1993-May 1993 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Mancino, Larry, Jun 1993-Jul 1993 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Mancino, Larry, Aug 1993-Sep 1993 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Mancino, Larry, Oct 1993-Dec 1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Mancino, Larry, Jan 1994-Mar 1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Mancino, Larry, Apr 1994-Jun 1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Mancino, Larry, Jul 1994-Sep 1994 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Mancino, Larry, Oct 1994-Dec 1994 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Mancino, Larry, Jan 1995 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Mancino, Larry, Feb 1995-Mar 1995 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Mancino, Larry, Apr 1995-Jun 1995 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Mancino, Larry, Jul 1995-Aug 1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Mancino, Larry, Sep 1995-Dec 1995 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Mancino, Larry, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Mancino, Larry: District 1, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Mancino, Larry: District 1, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Mancino, Larry: District 1, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Mancino, Larry: District 1, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Mancino, Larry: District 1, Local 1120, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Mancino, Larry: District 1, Local 1182, 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Mancino, Larry: Trenton, NJ Rally (May 2, 1995) (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Meetings, Jan 1986-Mar 1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Meetings, Apr 1986-Sep 1986 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Meetings, Oct 1986-Dec 1986 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Meetings, Jan 1987-Feb 1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Meetings, Mar 1987-May 1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Meetings, Jun 1987-Aug 1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Meetings, Sep 1987-Oct 1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Meetings, Nov 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Meetings, Jan 1988 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Meetings, Feb 1988 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Meetings, Mar 1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Meetings, Apr 1988-May 1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Meetings, Jun 1988-Aug 1988 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Meetings, Sep 1988-Oct 1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Meetings, Nov 1988-Dec 1988 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Meetings, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Members, 1987-1991 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Meetings, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Meetings, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Members: District 1, Jan 1989-Jul 1989 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Members: District 1, Aug 1989-Oct 1989 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Members: District 1, Nov 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Members: District 1, Jan 1990-Jun 1990 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Members: District 1, Jul 1990-Dec 1990 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Members: District 1, Jan 1991-Jun 1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Members: District 1, Jul 1991-Aug 1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Members: District 1, Sep 1991-Dec 1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Members: District 1, Jan 1992-Jul 1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Members: District 1, Aug 1992-Dec 1992 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Members: District 1, Jan 1993-May 1993 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Members: District 1, Jun 1993-Aug 1993 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Members: District 1, Sep 1993-Dec 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Members: District 1, Jan 1994-Feb 1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Members: District 1, Mar 1994-Apr 1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Members: District 1, May 1994-Jun 1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Members: District 1, Jul 1994-Aug 1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Members: District 1, Sep 1994-Dec 1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Members: District 1, Jan 1995-Feb 1995 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Members: District 1, Mar 1995 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Members: District 1, Apr 1995-Jun 1995 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Members: District 1, Jul 1995-Aug 1995 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Members: District 1, Sep 1995-Oct 1995 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Members: District 1, Nov 1995-Dec 1995 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Members: District 1, Mar 1996-Jul 1996 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Members: District 1, Aug 1996-Oct 1996 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Members: District 1, Nov 1996-Dec 1996 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Members: District 2, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Members: District 2, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Members: District 2, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Members: District 2, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Members: District 2, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Members: District 2, Jan 1994 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Members: District 2, Feb 1994-Dec 1994 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Members: District 2, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Members: District 2, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Members: District 3, Jan 1989-May 1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Members: District 3, Jun 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Members: District 3, Jan 1990-May 1990 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Members: District 3, Jun 1990-Dec 1990 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Members: District 3, Jan 1991-Jun 1991 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Members: District 3, Jul 1991-Dec 1991 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Members: District 3, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Members: District 3, Jan 1993-Sep 1993 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Members: District 3, Oct 1993-Dec 1993 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Members: District 3, Jan 1994-May 1994 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Members: District 3, Jun 1994-Aug 1994 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Members: District 3, Sep 1994-Dec 1994 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Members: District 3, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Members: District 3, Jan 1996-Jun 1996 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Members: District 3, Jul 1996-Dec 1996 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Members: District 4, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Members: District 4, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Members: District 4, Jan 1991 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Members: District 4, Mar 1991-Dec 1991 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Members: District 4, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Members: District 4, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Members: District 4, Jan 1994-May 1994 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Members: District 4, Jun 1994-Dec 1994 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Members: District 4, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Members: District 4, Jan 1996-May 1996 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Members: District 4, Jun 1996-Dec 1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Members: District 6, Jan 1989-Apr 1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Members: District 6, May 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Members: District 6, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Members: District 6, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Members: District 6, Feb 1992-Jul 1992 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Members: District 6, Aug 1992-Dec 1992 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Members: District 6, Jan 1993-Mar 1993 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Members: District 6, Apr 1993-Dec 1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Members: District 6, Jan 1994-May 1994 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Members: District 6, Jun 1994-Dec 1994 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Members: District 6, Jan 1995-Apr 1995 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Members: District 6, May 1995-Dec 1995 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Members: District 6, Jan 1996-May 1996 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Members: District 6, Jun 1996-Jul 1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Members: District 6, Aug 1996-Dec 1996 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Members: District 7, Jan 1989-Aug 1989 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Members: District 7, Sep 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Members: District 7, Mar 1990-Jun 1990 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Members: District 7, Jul 1990-Dec 1990 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Members: District 7, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Members: District 7, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Members: District 7, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Members: District 7, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Members: District 7, Jan 1995-Jun 1995 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Members: District 7, Jul 1995-Dec 1995 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Members: District 7, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Members: District 9, Jan 1989-Jul 1989 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Members: District 9, Aug 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Members: District 9, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Members: District 9, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Members: District 9, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Members: District 9, Jan 1993-Jun 1993 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Members: District 9, Jul 1993-Dec 1993 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Members: District 9, Jan 1994-Jul 1994 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Members: District 9, Aug 1994-Dec 1994 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Members: District 9, Jan 1995-Aug 1995 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Members: District 9, Sep 1995-Dec 1995 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Members: District 9, Jan 1996-May 1996 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Members: District 9, Jun 1996-Dec 1996 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Members: District 13, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Members: District 13, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Members: District 13, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Members: District 13, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Members: District 13, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Members: District 13, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 20)